(Leonard:)Oh, congratulations.
(Leonard:)Have you broken it
to the troll yet?
(Howard:)Did Penny tell you about that?
(Leonard:)No. Steve Patterson told me.
(Howard:)The greasy old fat guy
in Facilities Management?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
How'd he know about it?
(Leonard:)He's Glissinda the troll.
(Raj(voice):)Sorry, dude,
(Raj(voice):)the thermostat's
on my side of the room,
(Raj(voice):)so it stays Mumbai hot
in here until you turn off
that stupid Indian music!
(Sheldon(voice):)I'll turn off the music
(Sheldon(voice):)when you get rid of that
salmonella-ridden parakeet!
(Raj(voice):)Oh, too bad! Sheldon's
pathologically
afraid of birds!
(Raj(voice):)Hey, look, Sheldon!
Birdie, birdie, birdie!
(Sheldon(voice):)That's it! Prepare
for marshmallow death!
(Raj(voice):)Eat flaming Nerf!
(Leonard:)So anyway...
(Leonard:)That's great news
about you and Bernadette.
(Howard:)Yeah. I think I'm gonna take
her to miniature golf.
(Leonard:)Ah. Well, I guess
(Leonard:)for you guys that's
like regular golf.